A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.30 (A2004) FA482
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.30 (A2004)
1978-2005
1993-2003
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA482
93.01 Cubic Feet 71 standard record storage boxes.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2004.
Arrangement
Reccords are primarily arranged by Program.
Some subgroups may contain portions of the material that are arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Biographical / Historical
Rockefeller Foundation
The Rockefeller Foundation was established by act of the New York State Legislature approved by the Governor on May 14, 1913, "to promote the well-being of mankind throughout the world." Between 1913 and 1928 the China Medical Board, the International Health Board, and the Division of Medical Education functioned as divisions of the Foundation, concentrating on the administration of programs in public health and medical education. A Division of Studies was created in 1923 to handle projects outside the medical field. These early years were experimental as the new foundation studied the methods of philanthropy and explored its relationships with other Rockefeller boards. Although the Rockefeller Foundation is the largest and best known philanthropy founded by the Rockefeller family, it was neither the first nor the last to be established. The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (1901), the General Education Board (1902), the Rockefeller Sanitary Commission for the Eradication of Hookworm Disease (1909), and the Bureau of Social Hygiene (1911) all existed earlier. When the Foundation was created, the Sanitary Commission was disbanded. After the establishment of the Foundation, the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (1918) and the International Education Board (1923) were created.
The Rockefeller boards and their programs were reconsidered and reorganized in 1927-1928 in order to avoid overlapping programs. The International Health Board of the Foundation was disbanded and an International Health Division was organized. The China Medical Board, Inc., was established as a separately incorporated institution, and the China Medical Board of the Foundation ceased to exist. The Division of Studies was dropped and the Division of Medical Education was phased out. The Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial was combined with the Foundation and the Spelman Fund of New York was chartered to continue activities of the LSRM that were not absorbed by the Foundation. The International Education Board was disbanded.
As a result of this reorganization, the Foundation adopted a program which included public health work (administered by the IHD), the advancement of knowledge in the medical and natural sciences (in part taken over from the IEB), the social sciences (formerly the field of the LSRM), and the humanities and arts (shared with the GEB). The Rockefeller Institute and the Bureau of Social Hygiene were not affected by the reorganization. The program adopted by the Foundation at this time remained basically the same for the next twenty years.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
Grant administration files and related material.
- AC.2004.016: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-2001; AC.2004.016; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, R3632-R3637.; 6 standard record storage boxes, R3632-R3637.
  - Fellowships (F), AC.2004.016.1; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
    - F-AS INDIA AARTI, MS., 1997-1999 (Box R3632)
    - F-AS SYRIA AL-BALIBI, SALIM, 1996-1998 (Box R3632)
    - F-AS PHILIPPINES ALCANTARA, EDWIN PLATA, 1992-1998 (Box R3632)
    - F-AS BANGLADESH ALI, MD. LIAKAT, 1994-2000 (Box R3632)
    - F-AS PHILIPPINES ALVAREZ, NESTOR L., 1996-1999 (Box R3632)
    - F-AS INDIA ANANDA KUMAR, C.R., 1995-1997 (Box R3632)
    - F-AS PHILIPPINES ARDALES, EDNA YRAY, 1997-1999 (Box R3632)
    - F-AS INDIA BAJAJ, SHAVINDRA, 1997-2000 (Box R3632)
    - F-AS PAKISTAN BANO, SHAHINA, 1996-1998 (Box R3632)
    - F-AS UGANDA BASHAASHA, BERNARD, 1993-1998 (Box R3632)
    - F-AS ZIMBABWE BEPETE, MARTIN, 1992-2000 (Box R3632)
    - F-AS INDIA BHARATHI, MUTHUSAMY, 1996-1999 (Box R3632)
    - F-AS INDIA BHATTACHARJEE, BIOJOYA, 1997-2000 (Box R3632)
    - F 93151 - (ZIMBABWE)(F-AS) CHITEKA, ZVENHAMO ALBERT, 1989-1997 (Box R3633)
    - F 94042 - (ZIMBABWE)(F-AS) GUBBA, AUGUSTINE, 1994-2000 (Box R3633)
    - F 95030 - (CHINA)(F-AS) CHENG WEIZHONG, 1995-1997 (Box R3633)
    - F 96017 - (VIETNAM)(F-AS) DAO VIET BAG, 1996-1998 (Box R3633)
    - F 96039 - (VIETNAM)(F-AS) BONG, BUI BA, 1996-1997 (Box R3633)
    - F 96041 - (VIETNAM)(F-AS) DUG, LE TAN, 1996-1997 (Box R3633)
    - F 96078 - (INDIA)(F-AS) GARG, AJAY KUMAR, 1996-2001 (Box R3633)
    - F 96093 - (CHINA)(F-AS) HE ZUHUA, 1996-2000 (Box R3633)
    - F 96100 - (CHINA)(F-AS) FAN JUN, 1996-1998 (Box R3633)
    - F 97006 - (INDIA)(F-AS) CHANDRAKANTH, E., 1997-2001 (Box R3633)
    - F 97066 - (CAMEROON)(F-AS) FONDONG, VINCENT NGEPWUNG, 1997-2000 (Box R3633)
    - F 97068 - (INDIA)(F-AS) CHHABRA, ASHOK KUMAR, 1997-2000 (Box R3633)
    - F-AS ETHIOPIA HIRUT KEBEDE, 1997-2000 (Box R3634)
    - F-AS BANGLADESH HUQ, MD. ENAMUL, 1993-1999 (Box R3634)
    - F-AS MALAWI JAMU, DANIEL MATTHEWS, 1993-1998 (Box R3634)
    - F-AS INDIA JAYAPRAKASH, T. L., 1996-1999 (Box R3634)
    - F-AS INDIA KANT, TARUN, 1997-1999 (Box R3634)
    - F-AS PAKISTAN KHAN, MUHAMMED SARWAR, 1997-1999 (Box R3634)
    - F-AS INDIA - KHARB, PUSHPA, 1997-2001 (Box R3634)
    - F-AS UGANDA KIIZA, BARNABAS A., 1993-2000 (Box R3634)
    - F-AS CHINA KONG LINGQI, 1995-1998 (Box R3634)
    - F-AS IVORY COAST KOUASSI KOFFI II NAZAIRE, 1994-1997 (Box R3634)
    - F-AS INDIA KUMAR, ARUN, 1991-1992 (Box R3634)
    - F 92165 - (KENYA)(F-AS) MUGENDI, DANIEL N., 1992-1999 (Box R3635)
    - F 93086 - (ZIMBABWE)(F-AS) MACHADO, STEPHEN, 1993-1999 (Box R3635)
    - F 93147 - (KENYA)(F-AS) NANG'AYO, FRANCIS LEONARD OCHIENG, 1993-1997 (Box R3635)
    - F 94016 - (COSTA RICA)(F-AS) MUNOZ-FONSECA,. MIGUEL EDUARDO, 1994-1999 (Box R3635)
    - F 95023 - (UGANDA)(F-AS) NANKINGA, CAROLINE, 1995-2001 (Box R3635)
    - F 95039 - (CHINA)(F-AS) LUO LIJUN, 1995-1998 (Box R3635)
    - F 95055 - (ZIMBABWE)(F-AS) MEHLO, LUKE, 1995-1999 (Box R3635)
    - F 95056 - (ZIMBABWE)(F-AS) MAZITHULELA, GATSHA, 1995-1999 (Box R3635)
    - F 96042 - (CHINA)(F-AS) LU CHAOFU, 1996-1998 (Box R3635)
    - F 96083 - (CHINA)(F-AS) LI JIMING, 1996-2001 (Box R3635)
    - F 92145 - (ZIMBABWE)(F-AS) NDLOVU, ZIBUSISO, 1992-1997 (Box R3636)
    - F 92172 - (KOREA)(F-AS) OH SANG-SOO, 1992-1998 (Box R3636)
    - F 93146 - (BANGLADESH)(F-AS) PATHAN, MD. SAFIULLAH, 1993-2000 (Box R3636)
    - F 94067 - (KENYA)(F-AS) NGURE, STEPHEN MUGO, 1994-1999 (Box R3636)
    - F 94070 - (KENYA)(F-AS) ODHIAMBO, GEORGE DUNCAN, 1994-1998 (Box R3636)
    - F 94106 - (ZIMBABWE)(F-AS) NYAMUDEZA, PHIBION, 1994-1998 (Box R3636)
    - F 95094 - {VIETNAM)(F-AS) NGUYEN VAN DONG, 1995-1998 (Box R3636)
    - F 96003 - {CAMEROON)(F-AS) NDJIONDJOP, MARIE-NOELLE NZENKAM, 1996-1999 (Box R3636)
    - F 96024 - (VIETNAM)(F-AS) NGUYEN THI VINH, 1996-1999 (Box R3636)
    - F 97013 - (INDIA)(F-AS) NATH, UTPAL, 1997-2003 (Box R3636)
    - F 97028 - {INDIA)(F-AS) RAI, MAMTA, 1997-2000 (Box R3636)
    - F 97029 - (INDIA)(F-AS) PAREEK, ASHWANI, 1997-1998 (Box R3636)
    - F 92036 - (PHILIPPINES)(F-AS) SAMONTE, STANLEY OMAR PB., 1992-1997 (Box R3637)
    - F 95005 - (GUYANA)(F-AS) ROBERTS, CYRIL SEBASTIAN, 1995-1997 (Box R3637)
    - F 95061 - (MALAW l)(F-AS) SAKALA, WEBSTER DENIS, 1995-1998 (Box R3637)
    - F 96021 - (INDIA)(F-AS) RENGANAYAKI, KRISHNA R, 1996-2000 (Box R3637)
    - F 96037 - (CHINA)(F-AS) SHEN YUWEI, 1996-1999 (Box R3637)
    - F 96040 - (INDIA )(F-AS) RAMANATHAN, VAIRAMANI, 1995-1999 (Box R3637)
    - F 96063 - (INDIA)(F-AS) RAVI, K.S., 1996-1998 (Box R3637)
    - F 96101 - (INDIA)(F-AS )SIVARAJ, RAMASWANY, 1996-1999 (Box R3637)
    - F 97007 - (INDIA)(F-AS) ROY, MALABIKA, 1997-1999 (Box R3637)
    - F 97037 - (INDIA)(F-AS) SARIAL, ASHOK KUMAR, 1997-1999 (Box R3637)
    - F 97063 - (INDIA)(F-AS) SHARMA, PARVEEN KUMAR, 1997-1999 (Box R3637)
    - F 98001 - (INDIA)(F-AS) SINGH, KRISHNAN PAL, 1998-1999 (Box R3637)
    - F 98011 - (INDIA)(F-AS) ROBIN, SABARIAPPAN, 1998-1999 (Box R3637)
- AC.2004.017: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2002; AC.2004.017; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3638-R3639.; 2 standard record storage boxes, R3638-R3639.
  - Fellowships (F), AC.2004.017.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - F 93125 - (UGANDA)(F-AS) SSERUNKUUMA, DICK, 1993-1998 (Box R3638)
    - F 94035 - (COLOMBIA)(F-AS) TAPIERO-ORTIZ, ANIBAL LEONIDAS, 1994-2000 (Box R3638)
    - F 95007 - (INDIA)(F-AS) VALASUBRAMANIAN, R., 1995-1997 (Box R3638)
    - F 95033 - (INDIA)(F-AS) VELAZHAHAN, RETHINASAMY, 1995-1997 (Box R3638)
    - F 95089 - (INDIA)(F-AS) VIJAYACHANDRA, K., 1995-1997 (Box R3638)
    - F 95090 - (MALl)(F-AS) TOURE, ABOUBACAR, 1995-1998 (Box R3638)
    - F 95111 - (INDIA )(F-AS) THARA, KRISHNARAJPURAM V., 1996-1998 (Box R3638)
    - F 96008 - (INDIA)(F-AS) SUDHAKAR, DURAIALAGARAJA, 1996-2000 (Box R3638)
    - F 96016 - (VIETNAM)(F-AS) TRAN THI CUC HOA, 1996-1999 (Box R3638)
    - F 96034 - (INDIA)(F-AS) SUBBU, RAMA SUBBU SAMI, 1996-1999 (Box R3638)
    - F 96082 - (INDIA)(F-AS) TRIPATHY, JATINDRA NATH, 1996-2000 (Box R3638)
    - F 94125 - (CHINA)(F-AS) ZHONG JINGPING, 1994-1998 (Box R3639)
    - F 95041 - (CHJNA)(F-AS) ZHAO JUN, 1995-1998 (Box R3639)
    - F 95110 - (CHJNA)(F-AS) XU YUNBI, 1994-1999 (Box R3639)
    - F 96002 - (SOUTH KOREA)(F-AS) YOU TAEK HYON, 1996-1999 (Box R3639)
    - F 96023 - (CHINA)(F-AS) ZHAO BING-YU, 1996-1998 (Box R3639)
    - F 96043 - (CHINA)(F-AS) WANG JINGZHAO, 1996-1999 (Box R3639)
    - F 96064 - (CHINA)(F-AS) WANG DAOLONG, 1996-1998 (Box R3639)
    - F 97036 - (INDIA)(F-AS) YADAV, RAM CHANDER, 1997-2002 (Box R3639)
- AC.2004.024: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1992-2002; AC.2004.024; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3640-R3641.; 2 standard record storage boxes, R3640-R3641.
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2004.024.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - AH 9352; EO 9329 - AMERICAN ACADEMY OF ARTS AND SCIENCES - "SOCIAL CAPITAL AND PUBLIC AFFAIRS", 1992-2001 (Box R3640)
    - AH 9444 - UNITED STATES HOLOCAUST MEMORIAL COUNCIL - DESTRUCTION OF SOCIAL AND CULTURAL CAPITAL, 1994-2000 (Box R3640)
    - AH 9816 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - "INTERNATIONALIZI NG THE STUDY OF AMERICAN HISTORY, 1997-2002 (Box R3640)
    - AH 9823 - NEW ENGLAND FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - SYSTEM FOR COMMISSIONING AND TOURING OF NEW WORK, 1998-2000 (Box R3640)
    - AH 9903 - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF ARTISTS' ORGANIZATIONS - LEADERSHIP DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE - CO-GENERATE PROJECT, 1998-2002 (Box R3640)
    - AH 9904 - ART INSTITUTE OF CHICAGO - ASSESS NEED FOR CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF ART AND ARTISTS IN SOCIETY, 1997-2001 (Box R3640)
    - AH 9907 - AMERICAN DANCE FESTIVAL - 1999 FESTIVAL SEASON AND EXCHANGE PROGRAM ON INTERNET, 1999-2000 (Box R3640)
    - AH 9908 - DANCING IN THE STREETS - ONSITE PERFORMANCE NETWORK, 1998-2002 (Box R3640)
    - AH 9909 - BRONX MUSEUM OF THE ARTS - SYMPOSIUM FOCUSING ON BRONX AS SITE FOR CREATION OF POPULAR CULTURE, 1999-2000 (Box R3640)
    - AH 9910 - UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS (URBANA-CHAMPAIGN) - CONFERENCE ON LATIN AMERICAN LITERARY AND CULTURAL STUDIES, 1998-2000 (Box R3641)
    - AH 9911 - RELACHE - LATIN AMERICAN ACTIVITIES OF MUSIC IN MOTION PROGRAM, 1993-2000 (Box R3641)
    - AH 9912 - ASSOCIATION OF PERFORMING ARTS PRESENTERS - "IMPROVING ACCESS: IMMIGRATION REGULATIONS AND INTERNATIONAL ARTISTS", 1999-2002 (Box R3641)
    - AH 9913 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - CONFERENCE ON SAFEGUARDING TRADITIONAL CULTURE AND FOLKLORE, 1999-2002 (Box R3641)
    - AH 9914 - LINCOLN CENTER FOR THE PERFORMING ARTS - "LINCOLN CENTER FESTIVAL '99" AND "THE PEONY PAVILION", 1999-2000 (Box R3641)
    - AH 9915 - RESOLUTION - UBUNTU 2000 PROJECT, 1998-2000 (Box R3641)
    - AH 9916 - CALIFORNININTERNATIONAL ARTS FOUNDATION - PRODUCE AND DISTRIBUTE BOOK ON 20TH CENTURY CUBAN ART, 1998-2004 (Box R3641)
    - AH 9917 - ISRAEL FESTIVAL - EXCHANGE MEETING BETWEEN CHOIRS AT FESTIVAL, 1999 (Box R3641)
    - AH 9922 - TECTONIC THEATER PROJECT, INC. - "LARAMIE PROJECT", 1999-2002 (Box R3641)
    - AH 9924 - 3-LEGGED DOG - INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY DEVELOPMENT PROJECT, "SHAPE OF TIME", 1999-2001 (Box R3641)
    - AH 9927 - DANCE THEATER WORKSHOP - "NEW EUROPE 1999 CONSORTIUM AND FESTIVAL", 1997-2000 (Box R3641)
    - AH 9929 - ALLIANCE FOR THE ARTS - ESTATE PROJECT FOR ARTISTS WITH AIDS, 1997-2001 (Box R3641)
    - AH 9918 - WORLD CONFERENCE ON RELIGION AND PEACE - STRATEGIC COMMUNICATIONS PLAN, 1999-2001 (Box R3641)
- AC.2004.028: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2003; AC.2004.028; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, R3642-R3647.; 6 standard record storage boxes, R3642-R3647.
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2004.028.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AH 9932 - NATIONAL ENDOWMENT FOR THE HUMANITIES - REGIONAL HUMANITIES CENTER INITIATIVE, 1999-2001 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9933 - ASSOCIATION OF RESEARCH LIBRARIES - BUILDING BLOCKS PROJECT OF NATIONAL INITIATIVE FOR A NETWORKED CULTURAL HERITAGE, 1999-2001 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9935 - PASSIM, INC. - MULTI-MEDIA PROJECT, "MEET THE THINKERS: TELESYMPOSIUM", 1995-2002 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9936 - CENTER FOR TRADITIONAL MUSIC AND DANCE - NEW YORK CULTURAL HERITAGE FUND, 1999-2000 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9939 - TIBET FUND - ACTIVITIES OF "WORLD FESTIVAL OF SACRED MUSIC", 1999-2001 (Box R3642)
      Separated Materials
      Digital materials have been separated from the file. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
      - World Festival of Sacred Music, 2004.028.002; compact disc
    - AH 9941 - HENSON INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL OF PUPPET THEATER - 2000 FESTIVAL, 1999-2001 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9946 - RINGSIDE - "OUTRAGEOUS ACTS: TRANSGRESSIVE, OUTLAWED, AND UNTIDY ACTION IN AMERICA", 1999-2003 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9947 - ROULETTE - MUSICAL WORK, "JENKINS AND JENKINS", 1999-2004 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9948 - ROXANNE DANCE FOUNDATION - "TALE EXCHANGE", 1999-2001 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9949 - SARA PEARSON AND PATRIK WIDRIG CO - DANCE WORK, "HEREAFTER", 1999-2004 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9950 - SCHOOL OF HARD KNOCKS - DANCE WORK, "REVERSE PSYCHOLOGY", 1999-2004 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9951 - SEVEN LOAVES - PUPPET THEATER WORK, "TWELVE IRON SANDALS", 1998-2004 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9952 - SEVEN STAGES - THEATER WORK, "DISREMEMBER ME", 1999-2004 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9953 - URBAN BUSH WOMEN - DANCE WORK, "SOUL DEEP", 1999-2000 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9954 - WOOLLY MAMMOTH THEATRE COMPANY - THEATER COLLABORATION, "SHAW COMMUNITY PLAYBUILDING PROJECT", 1999-2004 (Box R3642)
    - AH 9955 - WOOSTER GROUP - MIXED MEDIA THEATER WORK, "PHEDRE", 1999-2004 (Box R3642)
    - RF 99024 #416; AH 9945 - PUBLIC THEATER - "IN THE BLOOD", 1999-2001 (Box R3642)
  - African Initiatives (AI), AC.2004.028.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - Al 9721 - UNIVERSITY OF TENNESSEE - CONFERENCE ON HISTORICAL EXPERIENCES OF AFRICAN AND AFRICAN-AMERICAN WOMEN, 1997-2003 (Box R3642)
    - Al 9722 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN-MADISON - BREAKDOWN OF STATES IN AFRICA AND EURASIA, CONFERENCE, 1997-2002 (Box R3643)
    - Al 9807 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - INTERNATIONAL SCHOLARLY COLLABORATION WORKING GROUP, 1997-2003 (Box R3643)
    - Al 9808 - NATIONAL COUNCIL FOR RESEARCH ON WOMEN - ITS GLOBAL INITIATIVE TO DISCOURSE ON GENDER ISSUES, 1998-1999 (Box R3643)
    - Al 9902 - UNIVERSITY OF EAST ANGLIA (ENGLAND) - AFRICAN PARTICIPANTS AT COLLOQUIUM ON POLICYMAKING IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1998-2000 (Box R3643)
    - Al 9904 - NATIONAL COUNCIL FOR RESEARCH ON WOMEN - ENABLE AFRICAN SCHOLARS TO PARTICIPATE IN ITS GLOBAL INITIATIVE FOR 1999, 1999-2002 (Box R3643)
    - Al 9906 - CENTRE FOR AFRICAN FAMILY STUDIES (KENYA) - CONFERENCE ON REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 1999-2000 (Box R3643)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS), AC.2004.028.3; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - AS 9631 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - CASSAVA GENOTYPES AND ALTITUDE ADAPTATION, 1995-2001 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9720 - TECHNICAL INSTITUTE OF AGRICULTURE NO. 16 (MEXICO) - FALLOW VEGETATION AND MULTISTRATA AGROFORESTRY, 1997-2001 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9722 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - MINI-CONFERENCES ON FOOD SECURITY IN ASIA, 1997-1999 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9803 - CENTER FOR RESEARCH AND ADVANCED STUDIES (CINVESTAV) (MEXICO) - VIRUS RESISTANT POTATOES, 1995-2003 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9820 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - APPLIED MICROECONOMICS CAPACITY IN EAST AND SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1998-2001 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9831 - COMMONWEALTH SCIENTIFIC AND INDUSTRIAL RESEARCH ORGANIZATION (AUSTRALIA) - APOMIXIS RESEARCH, 1998-2002 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9835 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - INTEGRATED MANAGEMENT OF ORGANIC INPUTS FOR LOW INCOME FARMERS, 1998-2003 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9839 - CAMARA, YOUSSOUF - PROFITABILITY OF CASSAVA-BASED PRODUCTIONS SYSTEMS IN WEST AFRICA, 1998-2000 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9904 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - COVER AGRICULTURE AND FARMER EXPERIMENTATION TO IMPROVE SMALLHOLDER LIVELIHOODS IN TROPICS, 1998-2001 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9905 - EUROPEAN SOCIETY OF AGRONOMY (FRANCE) - THIRD INTERNATIONAL CROP SCIENCE CONGRESS, 1998-2000 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9912 - WORLD NEIGHBORS - SUSTAINABLE RECOVERY IN CENTRAL AMERICA AFTER MITCH HURRRICANE, 1998-2001 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9917 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - GIS FACILITY AT KAWANDA RESEARCH STATION IN UGANDA, 1995-2000 (Box R3643)
      - Uganda's Agroecological Zones, 2004.028.001; compact disc
    - AS 9922 - AFRICARE - BASELINE SURVEY ON LABOR PROCUCTIVITY AND FARM INCOME THROUGH VILLAGE PROCESSING OF CROPS, 1999-2002 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9910 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - BIOMETRICS IN KENYAN UNIVERSITIES, 1999-2001 (Box R3643)
    - AS 9924 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - N SOURCES AND LEGUMINOUS CROPPING SYSTEMS, 1999-2001 (Box R3644)
    - AS 9925 - KALIBA, ALOYCE R.M. - EVALUATION OF COMMUNITY-BASED WATER SUPPLY PROJECTS IN CENTRAL TANZANIA, 1999-2002 (Box R3644)
    - AS 9929 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - PROCEEDINGS OF 15TH ANNUAL CONFERENCE OF THE SOIL SCIENCE SOCIETY OF EAST ASIA, 1999-2001 (Box R3644)
    - AS 9934 - FUND FOR THE INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE OF AGRICULTURAL ECONOMISTS - XXIV INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE OF AGRICULTURAL ECONOMISTS, 1999-2002 (Box R3644)
    - AS 9937 - INTERNATIONAL LIVESTOCK RESEARCH INSTITUTE (KENYA) - WORKSHOP ON ENHANCING EAST AFRICAN CAPACITY IN BIOCHEMISTRY, 1999-2000 (Box R3644)
    - AS 9939 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - TRANSLATION TO PORTUGUESE OF FOOD POLICY AND POVERTY LITERATURE, 1998-2002 (Box R3644)
    - AS 9940 - OKUSAMI, TEMITOPE A. - PARTICIPATION IN SOIL RESOURCES CONFERENCE, 1999-2001 (Box R3644)
    - AS 9941 - UNIVERSITY OF HYDERABAD (INDIA) - "INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON LIFE SCIENCES IN THE NEXT MILLENNIUM", 1999-2002 (Box R3644)
    - AS 9942 - INTERNATIONAL COOPERATIVE CENTRE FOR AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH FOR DEVELOPMENT (FRANCE) - SYSTEMATIZATI ON OF FARMER PARTICIPATORY EXPERIENCES IN THE TROPICS, 1999-2003 (Box R3644)
    - AS 9944 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - DIRECTORY OF INNOVATIVE FARMER ENTREPRENEURS FORMATION OF NETWORK TO SHARE EXPERIENCES, 1999-2003 (Box R3644)
    - AS 9948 - MALAWI - AGRICULTURE AND LIVESTOCK DEVELOPMENT (MINISTRY OF) - STRIGA RESISTANT/TOLERANT GENOTYPES OF MAIZE, 1998-2002 (Box R3644)
  - BD, AC.2004.028.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - BD 9615 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - WORKING GROUP ON CIVIC CONSCIOUSNESS AND GOVERNANCE, 1996-2001 (Box R3644)
    - BD 9809 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - CRIMINALIZATION OF DELIQUENCY STUDY, 1998-2004 (Box R3644)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2004.028.5; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - EO 9423 - NATIONAL BUREAU OF ECONOMIC RESEARCH, INC. - "YOUTH UNEMPLOYMENT AND EMPLOYMENT IN ADVANCED COUNTRIES", 1994-1999 (Box R3644)
    - EO 9719 - TIDES CENTER - GRANTMAKERS FOR EDUCATION PROJECT, 1997-2003 (Box R3644)
    - EO 9729 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - CIVIL RIGHTS PROJECT, 1997-2001 (Box R3644)
    - EO 9730 - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF LA RAZA - DIRECT-MAIL MARKETING AND MEMBERSHIP CAMPAIGN, 1997-2002 (Box R3645)
    - EO 9734 - PUBLIC HEALTH INSTITUTE - WELFARE AND WORK WORKSHOP CURRICULUM DEVELOPMENT, 1997-1999 (Box R3645)
    - EO 9739 - UNIVERSITY OF DELAWARE - STRENGTHEN CAPACITIES OF LOCAL SCHOOL BOARD MEMBERS, 1997-2002 (Box R3645)
    - EO 9739 - UNIVERSITY OF DELAWARE - STRENGTHEN CAPACITIES OF LOCAL SCHOOL BOARD MEMBERS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1997-2002; 2 folders. (Box R3645)
    - EO 9805 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - NONPROFIT JOB PLACEMENT AND TRAINING PROVIDERS, 1998-2002 (Box R3645)
    - EO 9818 - MASSACHUSETTS ASSOCIATION OF COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT CORPORATIONS - COMMUNITY ORGANIZING DEMONSTRATION PROGRAM, 1997-2001 (Box R3645)
    - EO 9822 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - MEETINGS ON ON NON-PROFIT EMPLOYMENT PROVIDERS, 1998-2002 (Box R3646)
    - EO 9825 - UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS (CHICAGO) - DIALOGUE SERIES ON DEMOCRACY, DIVERSITY AND NEW MILLENNIUM DIRECTIONS, 1998-2002 (Box R3646)
    - EO 9831 - UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND (BALTIMORE) - META-ANALYSIS OF VOLUNTARY GOVERNMENT TRAINING PROGRAMS, 1997-2002 (Box R3646)
    - EO 9835 - TOCH, THOMAS - BOOK ON EDISON PROJECT AND EMERGING MARKETPLACE IN AMERICAN PUBLIC EDUCATION, 1998-2002 (Box R3646)
    - EO 9840 - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF LA RAZA - HISPANIC EMPLOYMENT POLICY PROJECT, 1995-2000 (Box R3646)
    - EO 9840 - NATIONAL COUNCIL OF LA RAZA - HISPANIC EMPLOYMENT POLICY PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1995-2000 (Box R3646)
    - EO 9912 - ERIKSON INSTITUTE - PROJECT MATCH EMPLOYMENT SERVICES PROGRAM, 1996-2000 (Box R3646)
    - EO 9914 - ECONOMIC POLICY INSTITUTE - STATE OF WORKING MEXICO DOCUMENT; REPORT ON TRACKING LABOR MARKET IN AN INDUSTRIALIZING ECONOMY, 1999-2001 (Box R3646)
    - EO 9915 - PUERTO RICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATION FUND, INC. - MERGER TRANSITION WITH INSTITUTE FOR PUERTO RICAN POLICY; TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE AND STRATEGIC PLANNING, 1999-2003 (Box R3646)
    - EO 9917 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - COMMUNITY ARTS PARTNERSHIP, 1999-2002 (Box R3646)
    - EO 9920 - INSTITUTE FOR DEMOCRACY STUDIES - AFFIRMATIVE ACTION PROJECT OF ITS LAW AND DEMOCRACY PROGRAM, 1999-2001 (Box R3646)
    - EO 9908 - GREENSBORO JUSTICE FUND, INC. - PROGRAM ON THE 20TH ANNIVERSARY OF GREENSBORO MASSACRE, 1999 (Box R3646)
    - EO 9926 - HAYGROUND SCHOOL - OUTREACH EFFORTS; HIRING OF DIRECTOR, 1999-2001 (Box R3647)
    - EO 9928 - CHILDREN NOW - CHILDREN AND THE MEDIA PROGRAM, 1999-2001 (Box R3647)
    - EO 9934 - SUCCESS FOR ALL FOUNDATION - ROOTS AND WINGS AND SUCCESS FOR ALL PROGRAMS, 1998-1999 (Box R3647)
    - EO 9935 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY (TEACHERS COLLEGE) - PUBLICATION AND DISSEMINATION OF ARTICLES FROM BOOK, RECONSTRUCTING THE COMMON GOOD IN EDUCATION..., 1999-2001 (Box R3647)